{
    "id": "f9c93bdb390b4afa9c0482a33465b55b",
    "title": "Good And Well",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "That was a ………………….. movie.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "200259d26968442bb5af4a7eb590d968"
        },
        {
            "question": "The steak smells ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "090ef39afcdb472d8622e6b4b3b4efc0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is doing ……………… in his studies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "29f88d0acb554c15816fcb8330d5cca4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The proposal sounds ……………….. to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c7b23954852a4d299c1848111b47b0b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "That necklace looks …………………. on you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fa94d9a847374146a870b5815529268a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t have a ……………… opinion about him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "99cd8c77355046d38b77d5171087a4ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "She speaks English very …………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well",
                "good"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "624925425fc748a690ec60e0e220f342"
        },
        {
            "question": "The performance was remarkably ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well",
                "good"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e3939523336f42429a9f3452d7914c67"
        },
        {
            "question": "She performed remarkably ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cb5cca22966c4a2cb2674177dfa24898"
        },
        {
            "question": "She gave me some ……………….. advice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "11e506f98e184f07b9a5f6aeb15f31c0"
        }
    ]
}